<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lets Tell Your Story on Alaska Print Brokers</title>
    <link>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lets Tell Your Story on Alaska Print Brokers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 14:12:30 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:30:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/services/</guid>
      <description>Design, Consulting, Project Management and Editing Services It&amp;rsquo;s one thing to write a book. It&amp;rsquo;s another thing to put one together. We have fulltime editors and designers on staff that are ready to help you get the polish on your book that really makes it shine. For example, do you have cover art for your book? We can source from some fantastic artists (both locally and around the world!) to really make your book stand out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 14:12:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to get started? Or are you just looking for some info before you do? Feel free to contact us at whatever stage you&amp;rsquo;re at in your literary journey. We&amp;rsquo;re happy to answer any of your questions or provide a quote!
 Contact:
Mike Tucker
Phone: 907-929-5523
Email: mike@alaskaprintbrokers.com
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Us</title>
      <link>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/why-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 14:12:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/why-us/</guid>
      <description>It today&amp;rsquo;s world there are lots of ways to publish a book. Some require good connections or an established reputation (traditional publishing), others require quite a bit of technical know-how (self-publishing). But we aim to make it easy for you no matter what position your in.
Alaska Print Brokers, a subsidiary of Todd Communications is an Anchorage-based company specializing in the needs of publishers, authors, photographers and fine artists in Alaska who want their projects printed and delivered without the headaches that usually occur when they try to handle it by themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some of Our Work</title>
      <link>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 14:11:58 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/work/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 14:07:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://admiralrob.github.io/apb/history/</guid>
      <description>Alaska Print Brokers is an Anchorage-based company specializing in finding the best printers in North America and Asia to meet the needs of West Coast publishers, authors, photographers and fine artists. The company evolved out of Alaska Color Scan, which brought the first scanner to Alaska in 1982. This Crosfield 510 drum scanner provided the latest scanner technology to a market that had never had locally available color separations before. That company provided color separations to every newspaper and printing company in Alaska capable of printing color in the 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
